Hello!
مرحباً!
You have just received your new prosthesis at Ortho Espace 3D.
لقد تلقيت للتو طرفك الاصطناعي الجديد في Ortho Espace 3D.
The first days are an important adaptation period.
الأيام الأولى هي فترة تكيف مهمة.
Here are our tips to get started well.
إليك نصائحنا لبداية جيدة.
Fitting the prosthesis.
التركيب.
Start by putting the liner on your residual limb, ensuring there are no folds.
ابدأ بلبس البطانة على جذعك مع التأكد من غياب أي طيات.
Check that the skin is well tensioned.
تأكد من أن الجلد ممتد جيداً.
Then attach the prosthesis according to your device's attachment system.
ثم ضع الطرف الاصطناعي وفقاً لنظام التثبيت الخاص بجهازك.
Building up wear time.
التدرج في الاستخدام.
Start with two hours per day and increase gradually.
ابدأ بساعتين يومياً وزد تدريجياً.
In the first week, aim for four to six hours.
في الأسبوع الأول، استهدف أربع إلى ست ساعات.
If pain appears, remove the prosthesis and contact us.
إذا ظهر ألم، انزع الطرف الاصطناعي وتواصل معنا.
The condition of your skin.
حالة جلدك.
After each wear, carefully inspect the entire residual limb.
بعد كل استخدام، افحص جذعك بعناية.
A slight redness that disappears in twenty minutes is normal.
الاحمرار الخفيف الذي يختفي في عشرين دقيقة أمر طبيعي.
However, persistent redness, a wound or blisters require a consultation.
أما الاحمرار المستمر أو الجرح أو البثور فتستوجب استشارة طبية.
Rehabilitation.
إعادة التأهيل.
Physical therapy is essential to regain your independence.
العلاج الطبيعي ضروري لاستعادة استقلاليتك.
Work on balance, walking and muscle strengthening at your own pace.
اعمل على التوازن والمشي وتقوية العضلات بإيقاعك الخاص.
Our team at Ortho Espace 3D coordinates your follow-up.
فريقنا في Ortho Espace 3D ينسق متابعتك.
Our practitioners are available to answer all your questions.
متخصصونا متاحون للإجابة على جميع أسئلتكم.
Do not hesitate to call us or send us a message on WhatsApp.
لا تترددوا في الاتصال بنا أو إرسال رسالة عبر واتساب.
Courage — you are not alone!
شجاعة — لستم وحدكم!